Transcription by CastingWords
It was my first day as a high school junior.
Everyone, take a seat.
I knew Brother was starting his new job here, but this couldn't be happening.
I never imagined he would be my homeroom teacher.
I was so happy.
I would be able to see him every day at school.
Hey, Mr. Kanai!
I'm not going to do this.
Ah, Mr. Kanai, one of your students.
Oh, you brought me the handouts. Thanks.
It's been a long time that I've been watching you, Brother.
That's why I noticed him making a face before he did.
One I've never seen him make before.
I'm so stupid.
I let my guard down.
I can't believe that stupid little middle-aged chick could wiggle herself in there!
Huh?
You know, I can't believe how much Hana has mellowed out.
Really?
She's just being polite because you're here, sweetie.
Please, Mom, chill.
Yeah, yeah.
Ah, delicious.
Obviously.
You're so lucky your mother has always been such a good cook.
That's very kind of you, dear.
But Hana actually helped me out this time around.
She almost never does that.
Mom, stop it!
Well, regardless, it turned out to be very delicious.
I'm so angry.
Thanks again for the wonderful meal.
To think I feel so saved by such a meaningless little thing.
Even though it's pointless to hope.
We're neighbors, after all.
Homemade cooking is the best.
It's only me and Pops at home, you know.
Neither of us can really cook.
I need one soon.
Hmm.
Here he goes.
I can't wait to have a wonderful wife.
It's something he always says.
He's been saying it ever since junior high.
But lately he hasn't bothered.
Is that...
Because he now has someone specific in mind?
That's amazing, Hana!
You got first place!
That's awesome!
I'm so jealous!
Hey!
Why didn't you run with your actual mom or dad, Hana-bee?
Huh?
Yeah!
You're right!
He's too young!
That's not her dad!
Totally unfair!
Cheater!
Stop that, Norco!
Hana.
Shut up.
Huh?
You know what's really unfair?
Your stupid shoes!
Hey!
Hana-bee's right!
Hold on!
They told us we weren't allowed to wear those types of speed shoes during the races!
Is that true, Norco?
What did you get yourself into?
Hana?
Come on, Hana.
Uh...
Hey there.
I don't really care.
Hmm?
Running with you isn't unfair.
Norco's just a sore loser.
That's right.
Let's not forget, it's also not unfair for me to eat the lunch your mother packed for
you to have.
Really?
Mom said she had to work all day today!
She stayed up late to make this for you, so then we should probably eat it all.
Okay!
It's...
so good!
This is just average.
Hana, someday you will appreciate having a mother that can cook for you.
Maybe you're right, but you went fishing with your father.
Hmm?
I don't have a dad I can go fish with.
You make me feel jealous.
I understand.
Well, then it looks like we both have something the other is jealous of.
That's good, I guess.
We can help each other when we feel lonely.
Fire!
Miss Minagawa's so friggin' hot.
The new music teacher?
She's not old either.
She's close to our age, right?
Huh?
Hey, is that Hanabi looking at us over there?
Really?
Is she looking at me?
Don't be stupid.
It's me.
Oh!
I'm so sorry!
Are you injured?
Are you okay there?
Long length hair.
Lame beige cardigan.
Strong smell of boring old people shampoo.
Natural style basic makeup.
Here you go, Miss Minagawa.
Thank you, dear.
You're sweet, Mugi.
We're at school right now.
Miss Minagawa.
Oh, dearie me!
That's right!
Jeez, I've done it again!
Who is this guy?
Another one of her fanboys?
I can't believe this is happening.
How embarrassing!
Please forgive me!
Huh?
No.
I recognize that.
The look in his eyes.
Hey.
Huh?
I'm sorry, but do you know who she likes?
I do.
What a coincidence.
Akane was my tutor back when I was in junior high.
I never would have thought she would actually become a teacher in my high school.
At first, I thought I was really lucky to have her here.
Are you listening?
What's so special about a basic woman like her?
Hey there, don't you dare go insulting Akane.
Yeah, yeah.
Guys like those sweet, sempering, doe-eyed girls, don't they?
They were both very vindictive people in our longing.
Listen here!
And the stronger we felt for them,
the harder we moped.
Before we knew what was happening,
we were spending a lot of time with each other.
Ugh, I'm so done with this whole thing.
Hey, don't get my bed wet with your tears.
I just want to quit school and never come back.
You talking about Mr. Kanai?
You're just going to give him up?
I could never do that.
But?
But what?
I was just messing around.
At first, at least.
Huh?
You scared me.
Really?
I couldn't tell at all.
You sad?
Aren't you sad too, Mookie?
It took some time.
But I think we both were thinking the same thing.
Mookie doesn't have any lustful feelings for me like that.
Whether I see Mookie as Mookie or not,
it doesn't matter.
Hey, that tickles Mookie.
In the end,
I'm just a replacement too.
Do you even want to do this?
You're the one who wants to.
But you look nothing like him.
I don't know how you expect me to pretend.
You're way too demanding.
And I'm pretty good looking, you know?
Just close your eyes.
Yes.
If we're going to do this,
then we really do it.
Oh, crap.
What is this?
If I imagine that he's brother...
My fingertips are cold.
Everything feels so distant.
All I can hear is my heart.
Because...
This is what I've wanted from him.
Forever.
It was electric.
Did you know that was my first kiss?
No way.
Really.
It felt good.
One more time.
There's a part of me that worries.
Am I really being a good enough replacement for him?
Can he pretend?
It's okay.
These hands...
Our brother's hands...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
The things brother doesn't do.
The things he won't do for me.
The things I want to do to him.
I can't see his face.
He's so quiet.
I have to try to stay quiet, too.
I don't want to remind him it's me.
Concentrate.
Don't betray him.
Oh.
That's good.
He can't see my face like this.
I have to remember as much as possible.
Hold on to it.
Huh?
Who could that be?
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Ugh.
Why?
You done?
Huh?
Yeah.
I think that'll be enough for us today.
But, um...
You want to keep doing this?
Or stop?
I'm sorry.
I gave you my answer.
Goodbye.
Huh?
Wait.
I...
I waited a week for your answer.
You can't just...
Tease me here.
There's nothing more revolting than the complicated affection...
Of someone you're completely disinterested in.
Whoa.
Damn it.
Boomerang.
At that moment.
I had no answer.
I couldn't completely let go.
I don't mean Mugi.
I mean brother.
The brother I was seeing...
Through Mugi.
That's why I...
I'm surprised you came back here.
I didn't think that you would bother.
If you want, we can say that we're dating.
What?
We will both be able to depend on each other.
If needed.
You sure you won't fall in love with me and push your affections on both of us?
I won't.
I promise you.
You're completely not my type.
You're not mine.
And so we made a pact that neither of us would ever fall in love with the other one.
And if one of us makes it with the person we really love, our relationship ends.
In other words, you can have everything but my feelings.
That's the deal.
So I was thinking, does that basically make us friends with benefits?
No, no.
Hmm?
Not at all.
We didn't do it.
And we probably never will.
Yeah?
If one of us is feeling lonely, what's wrong with wanting the other to hold you?
Is that because I'm a virgin and you're scared to deflower me?
Huh?
Where did you get that idea?
You'll see in the end.
Our scum's wish will come true.